- 마셔요
- 고마워요
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
영화 한 편 같이 볼까?
"Say, Rachel...
...I was wondering if you'd
go to a movie with me sometime...
연인으로서!
...as my lover."
그건 심하고...
언제 식사나 같이 할까?
Too out there.
"Maybe you'd like to have
dinner with me sometime...
연인으로서!
...as my lover."
- 안녕
- 안녕, 마크
지금 갈까?
All right, let's go shopping.
그 전에, 잠깐 할 얘기가 있어
Before we go, there's something
I need to say.
그래
너를 많이 좋아하고 있어
I've kind of had this crush on you.
그 동안 로스 때문에
고백할 수가 없었지
Since you were with Ross,
I didn't do anything about it.
이젠 헤어졌으니까
데이트 신청해도 되지?
Now that you're not, I'd really
like to ask you out sometime.
그래서 오늘도 나온 거야
So that's what I'm doing...
... now.
컵 하나 깼어
I dropped a cup.
The One With the Tiny T-Shirt
몇 년 안에, 목소리 인식
컴퓨터가 일반화 될 거예요
So within a few years,
voice recognition...
...will be standard
on any computer.
그렇게 되면,
차 닦아, "방 치워"...
You know, so you could be, like,
"Wash my car." "Clean my room."
사실, 그 정도는 아니지만
사람 말은 인식할겁니다
It won't be able to do any of those
things, but it'll understand.
- 대단하네요
- 그래요
Oh, this was so great.
Yeah, it was.
그럼 이만
All right, then.
잘 가요
Bye.
여기 주인은 누굴까요?
Hello, people who do not live here.
어서 와
급할 때 쓰라고 준 열쇠야
I gave you a key for emergencies.
감자 칩이 떨어졌어
We were out of Doritos.
백만장자 씨와 데이트는
어땠어?
Hey, how'd the date go
with Mr. Millionaire?
'백만장자의 새로운
애인 탄생! '
"Mr. Millionaire.
New, from Snooty Playthings.
Third wife sold separately."
'세 번째 마누라도
갈아치우다'
너무 좋아
He's great. We have such
a good time together.
즐거운 시간이었어
재밌고 다정한 사람이야
He's so funny and so sweet.
And I'm not attracted to him at all!
그런데 좋아지지가 않아
Still?
아직도?
안돼!
나도 미치겠어
It's driving me crazy. In every
other way, he's the perfect guy.
모든 면에서 완벽한 남자야
모든 걸 갖췄어
He has everything.
Plus, he actually has everything.
게다가, 실제로
모든 걸 갖고 있지
실제 크기의 스타워즈
돌격대원 복장도 있대?
Life-sized lmperial Storm Troopers
from Sharper lmage?
두 개나
Two.
그럼 조이하고 내가
빌려 써 볼 수 없을까?
Can Joey and I put them on and fight?
Oh, Mommy! Oh, Daddy!
I am a big old baddy
어, 엄마! 아, 아빠!
난 멋진 놈이에요!
Oh, Mommy! Oh, Daddy!
I am a big old baddy
I guess he must've gotten the part
in that play.
연극에서 역할을 땄나보다
아님, 글로리아 에스테판이
환장할 거다
Either that, or Gloria Estefan
was right.
Eventually, the rhythm
is going to get you.
리듬을 저 따위로 망치냐!
- 기분 어때요?
- 좋죠
-Joe, how's it going?
-Good.
- 안녕하세요
- 안녕
So you're playing Adrianne?
에이드리안 역이군요?
네, 당신은 저능아들 중
한 명인가요?
Yes. Are you one of the
retarded cousins?
No. I'm playing your husband, Victor.
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
아뇨, 당신 남편 역 빅터에요
조이 트리비아니입니다
반가워요
케이트 밀러에요
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Kate Miller.
이번 연극 정말 좋죠?
So the play's pretty great, huh?
제니퍼 벤버리 작품이니까요
Oh, yeah.
I love Jennifer Banberry's work.
미국 중산층의 정신세계를
날카롭게 비판하고 있죠
She's so incisive when it comes
to deconstructing the middle class.
Oh, forget about it. She rocks!
그냥 한 마디로
끝내주죠
얼굴이 낯이 익어요
Where do I know you from?
Dr. Drake Ramoray?
드레이크 레모레이 박사
'우리의 날들' 알죠?
Days of our Lives?
10대들이 좋아했던
신경외과 의사 역이었죠
Voted most datable neurosurgeon
by Teen Beat?.
그건 아닌 것 같은데요
No, that's not it.
그럼 탤런트였군요
So you're a soap actor.
진짜 무대에 서니
꽤 흥분되시겠어요?
This must be exciting for you,
being in a real play.
연극도 많이 했어요
진짜 배우라구요
Hey, I've done plays before.
I'm a serious actor.
That infomercial!
광고방송!
우유상자가 터지는 거요!
우유도 못 따던 그 남자군요!
For the milk-carton-spout thing!
You're the guy who doesn't
know how to pour milk!
I actually can pour milk. But I got
you believing that I couldn't.
실제로는 잘 따는데
연기를 한 거죠
연기 잘하죠?
Now, see, that's acting.
과자 때문에 목이 메인
연기는 좋았어요
Right. At the end, you choked
on a cookie.
그건 진짜였어요
That was real.
- 마크가 그랬다니, 놀랍다
- 그래
-I cannot believe Mark asked you out.
-I know.
넌 뭐라고 할건데?
What are you gonna tell him?
생각해본다고 했는데
거절해야겠어
I told him I would think about it,
but I'm gonna tell him no.
I think I'd say no
to anybody right now.
누가 오든 다 거절할 거야
기분이 이상해
But it was so strange.
I mean, I'm standing there...
...with this charming, cute guy
who's asking me to go out with him...
매력적인 남자가
데이트하자고 하는데...
왠지 모르게
죄 짓는 느낌이 들어
...which I'm allowed to do...
...and I felt guilty, like I'd be
cheating on Ross or something.
로스 몰래 바람피우는
기분이야
그럼 로스에 대한 감정
정리가 안 된 거야
Wow. So, okay, maybe that means...
...you're not over Ross yet
and you have issues with your father.
아빠랑 의논해 봐
아빠한테 이런 얘길 왜 해?
-I don't have issues with my father.
-So it's just the Ross thing.
그럼 로스랑 하던지
그 여자 정말 싫어!
싫다구!
I hate this woman! I hate her!
She told everyone
about that infomercial...
광고 얘기를 떠들고 다녀서
다들 음료수 캔 따달라고 한다구
...and now they all keep asking me
to open their drinks!
그래서 못 따면...
웃고 난리야
And whenever I can't do it,
they're all, like, laughing at me!
- 안녕
- 어서 와
So Rachel called.
레이첼이 전화했어
만나고 싶대
Wants to see me.
곧 갈 거야
Going over in a minute.
레이첼이 뭐라고 할까?
-What do you think she wants?
-Maybe the crazy fog has lifted...
생각의 안개가 걷히자
삶이 어떤지 깨달은 거지
...and she realizes that life
without me...
...sucks.
'못 살아! '
It's possible. You are very lovable.
I'd miss you if I broke up with you.
당연해, 넌 사랑스럽거든
너랑 헤어지면
무척 그리울 거야
도와주려는 거야
Just trying to be supportive.
그럼 남자처럼 도와줘
Be supportive like a guy.
너랑 헤어지면
무척 그리울 거야
If I broke up with you, I'd miss you.
안녕
날...
보자고 했지?
You wanted to see me?
응
네 물건 가져가
Here's a box of your stuff.
뭐?
It's just hats and a shirt and CD's.
Just stuff that you've left here.
모자, 셔츠, CD 그런 거...
전부 네 물건이야
지금 뭐야?
상처나 받으라는 거야?
What are you doing? Are you trying
to hurt me or something?
아냐
이제 우리 사이를
정리할 때가 됐잖아
It just seems that, you know,
it's time we move on.
안 그래?
I mean, don't you think?
- 그래
- 좋아
-Yes, I do.
-Good.
- 진짜 그래
- 그럼...
나도 그러고 싶어
I really do.
이건... 선물이었어
This was a gift.
박물관 선물 가게에서
공짜로 얻은 거잖아
You got that for free
from the museum gift shop.
선물은 선물이지
선물 '가게'가 뭔데!
It's still a gift.
I got it from the "gift" shop.
알았어, 내가 가질게
이리 줘!
Okay! All right! Give me the mug!
I'll keep the mug!
싫어!
사정 봐줄 거 없어
Don't do me any favors.
In fact...
다른 물건은 어딨지?
...where's the rest of my stuff?
Like my....
그러니까...
이건 내 책이야!
This book is mine!
네가 잘 때 입던
셔츠도 돌려줘
And that T-shirt you sleep in?
I'd like that back too. Yes, I do.
You know how much I love that T-shirt.
You never even wear that T-shirt.
그건 내가 좋아하는 거야
넌 입지도 않잖아
널 도와주려는 거야
정리한다며?
I'm just trying to help you "move on."
Oh, you are a petty man.
넌 좀팽이야
쫀쫀한... 쫀쫀하기는
You are a petty, petty...
- 쫀쫀이...
- 좀팽이, 좀팽이
-Petty...
-... petty, petty...
- 밴댕이 속...
- 밴댕이 속!
-...small....
그렇게 심술부리는 거 아냐
You are so just doing this
out of spite.
아니, 아니지
이제 매일 입을 거야!
난 이 셔츠를 사랑해!
I'm gonna wear this all the time!
I love this shirt!
15살 때 입던 거라
이젠 맞지도 않을 텐데!
You haven't worn it since you were 15!
It doesn't even fit you anymore!
- 그래, 그래...
좋아, 좋아
프랭키 왈, 편히 쉬어
이제 됐지?
내 물건 다 가져갈게
If you don't mind, I'm gonna
take the rest of my stuff...
편히 쉴 거야
...and "relax"...
이 셔츠 입고...
...in my favorite shirt.
너도 편히 쉬어라
You have a pleasant evening.
So you're, like, a zillionaire.
천만장자라면서요?
우리랑 동년배죠?
동년배요
And you're our age.
You're our age.
You know what?
You should buy a state...
미국의 주를 하나 사서
당신 이름을 붙여봐요
...and then just name it
after yourself.
'피트 다코타'?
Like, "Pete Dakota"?
Or "Mississi-Pete."
아님... '미시시피트'
'피트 시카고' 어때요?
I got it: "Pete Chicago."
That's not a state, Joe.
그건 주가 아냐
Oh, and "Mississi-Pete" is?
미시시피는 주냐?
가야겠어요
나중에...
I gotta go.
- 또 봅시다
- 좋아요
I'll see you guys later.
우리가 동년배라니...
You're our age.
내일 만날 수 있죠?
So are we on for tomorrow?
- 물론이죠
- 좋아요
Absolutely.
조심해서 가세요!
Now, get out of here, you!
Okay, I'm running out of places
I can touch him.
이제 더 이상
만질 데도 없어
Is something wrong with me?
나한테 문제가 있는 거니?
나는 왜, 미래가 없는
남자만 좋아할까?
Why am I only attracted to guys
with no future?
Either they're too old,
or they're too young.
너무 늙거나, 너무 어리거나...
피트는 나한테 빠져있어
And there's Pete,
who's crazy about me...
...and he's absolutely perfect,
and there's zip going on!
저 완벽한 남자가
나를 정말로 좋아해!
정말 나한테
문제가 있는 거니?
Does it sound like
something's wrong with me?
응, 조금
Yeah, kind of.
행복?
이걸 행복이라고 해?
Happy? Is that what I'm
supposed to be, Vic?
행복?
Happy?
그럼 당신이 원하는
행복을 말해봐
Why don't you tell me what
you're supposed to be?
난 죽어도 모르겠으니까!
Because I sure as hell can't
figure it out!
I talk to you, and nothing!
그건 아무 것도 아냐!
날 봐, 아무 것도 아냐
You look at me, and it's nothing!
아무 것도!
Nothing.
감칠맛이야!
Tasty.
이제야 두 사람이
사연 많은 부부 같아요
I'm really starting to feel like
you guys have a history. It's nice.
좋아요
I have a question about this scene.
- 궁금한 게 있어요
- 네
에이드리언이 왜 빅터를
사랑하는 지 모르겠어요
I don't understand why Adrianne's
attracted to Victor.
양파 껍질을 벗겨요
Peel the onion.
First of all, he's good-looking.
- 일단, 잘생겼잖아요
- 맞아요
My character needs a bit more
of a reason than that.
배역 연기를 위해서
다른 설명을 해주세요
내가 해주죠
Hey, how about this one?
It says so in the script!
대본에 그렇게 써있어요!
I don't know why my character
likes you either.
나도 빅터가 이해 안 되요
대본을 보면, 당신은
싸가지가 없거든요
I mean, it says in the script
that you're a bitch.
-lt doesn't say that in the script.
-lt does in mine.
- 대본에 그런 말 없어요
- 내 대본엔 있어요
드라이를 하든, 젤을 바르든
소용이 없어
I can blow-dry it, gel it.
It doesn't matter.
이 가운데 들뜬 머리 때문에
신경 쓰여 죽겠어
I still wind up with this little...
...cowlick-y thing on the middle part
of my head. It's so annoying.
- 많이 티나?
- 네가 더 튀어
-Does it bug you?
-You bug me.
네가 안 볼 수 있는
방법이 없을까?
Is there any chance
you didn't see that?
로스, 그만 좀 해
Ross, you gotta stop, okay?
너 지금 그 좁은 구멍에
3시간이나 눈 대고 있어!
You can't stare through
the peephole for three hours.
그러다 눈 작아진다
You're gonna get peep-eye.
이럴 줄 알았어
마크를 좋아하고 있던 거야
I knew it. I knew it.
I always knew she liked him.
She'd say no, but here we are. We just
broke up, first thing she does!
아니라고 하더니
지금 꼴을 봐
헤어지자마자
마크부터 만나고 있잖아
헤어지자마자는 아니지
You didn't "just break up."
3주밖에 안 지났어!
It's been, like, three weeks!
네가 딴 여자랑 3시간 자고
헤어진 거야
You slept with somebody three hours
after you thought you broke up.
남의 똥만 커 보이지?
I mean, bullets have left guns slower.
나타났어, 온다...
키스하면 나 자살할 거야
Here they come! Here they
If she kisses him good night,
I'll kill myself.
더 이상 못 보겠어
I can't watch.
Come on.
Date over! Date over!
데이트는 끝났어!
집에 가
Here we go. She's going in.
됐어, 레이첼이 들어간다
레이첼이 들어가고
마크도 들어갔어
She's going in.
Wait! He's going in!
마크도 들어갔어!
He's going in!
문이 닫혔어!
문을 닫으면 안 보이잖아!
The door's closed! I can't see
anything with the door closed!
문을 발명하신 아저씨,
고이 잠드소서
And the inventor of the door
rests happily in his grave.
뭔가 해야돼
그러니까... 가서 막아야지
I have to do something.
I have to stop it!
-Stop what?
-I don't know.
- 뭘 막아?
- 잘은 몰라도...
분명히 그걸 할거야
But I have a feeling
my being there will do it.
가서 뭔가를 빌려야 돼
I'll go over and I will
borrow something!
주스! 주스가 필요해!
Juice! I need juice!
안돼!
- 갈 거야
- 안돼!
You can't!
가서 막아야돼
-They must be stopped!
-I am your friend...
친구로서, 기필코 널 막으마!
힘은 왜 이렇게 세!
...and I won't let you do this!
You are surprisingly strong!
주스가 필요해!
인간은 주스가 필요해!
-I need juice! People need juice!
-Look, man....
- 친구...
- 누구나 주스가 필요해
-People need juice!
-Listen to me!
- 내 말 들어
- 주스!둘이...
저건 당연한 거야
She's moving on. If it's not
this guy, it's gonna be somebody else.
이 남자가 아니라도
언젠가는 누굴 만나
And unless you're thinking about
subletting my peephole...
우리 집 문 앞에서
살 게 아니면
너희들이 끝났다는 걸
인정해야 돼
...you'll have to get used to the fact
that it's over!
Okay, man? It's over.
이미 끝났다구
- 그래, 맞아
- 됐어
레이첼이 너무 그리워
It's just I miss her so much.
알아
I know.
머그 잔 바닥에
웬 번호들이야?
Why do your coffee mugs have numbers?
Oh, that's so Monica can keep track.
모니카 버릇이야
하나라도 없어지면 이래
27번 어디 갔어?
So if one of them's missing,
she can be like, "Where's number 27?"
잠깐만...
You know what?
그 말에 느낌이 오네
No, and I don't think
I'm gonna want to.
아무래도 안 되겠어
-I can't do this.
-That's what I didn't want to know.
그래, 바로 이 느낌
내 욕심 때문에
너를 만난 거 같아
Oh, I'm just doing this
for the wrong reasons, you know?
로스에게 복수하려구
미안해, 이러면 안 되는데
I'm doing it to get back at Ross.
I'm sorry. It's not very fair to you.
안 되긴 뭐가!
Fair, shmair. You know?
로스에게 복수하고 싶으면
내가 도와줄게
You wanna get back at Ross,
I am here for you.
Really.
진심이야
I say we get back at him right here
on this couch. Right here!
바로 이 소파에서
로스에게 복수하자구
여기서!
세상에, 정말 미안해
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry about this.
괜찮아
That's okay.
- 정말?
- 응
You sure?
집에 가서 나 혼자
복수할게
I can just go home and get back
at him by myself.
21세기의 페니실린입니다
and should become the penicillin
of the 2 1st century.
오늘, 이 병원이 그 혁명의
선두주자로 나섭니다
And so today, this hospital
is about to take major steps...
...toward leading that revolution.
그리고, 오늘 이 자리는...
뭐 하나 물읍시다
Can I ask you something?
Where are we?
지금 우린 어디죠?
Well, with all these doctors
and nurses...
의사와 간호사가 있으니
로데오 경기장인가요?
... I'm gonna say, "Midget Rodeo."
솔직히 말해봐요
Just tell me the truth.
네...
이 말을 했는지 몰라도
You know, I don't think
I told you this...
최근에 실연의 상처를
극복했어요
... but I just recently got out
of a serious relationship.
Oh, right.
Wasn't that a year ago?
1년 전 그 일이요?
벌써 말했군요
So I did tell you.
That's not really the thing.
진짜 이유가 있죠
I'm just in a place in my life
where I need to focus on me.
전 지금, 인생에서
나 자신을 찾는 시점에 있어요
- 무슨 뜻인지 아시죠?
- 알아요
-Do you know what I mean?
-Oh, I know.
당신을 좋아하고 싶어요
-I so want to be attracted to you.
-But you're not. Okay. Good.
지금은 아니다 이거군요
죄송해요
I'm sorry.
미안해하지 말아요
괜찮아요, 힘들진 않네요
You know what? Don't be.
Don't be, because it's not so bad.
- 그래요?
- 네
It's not?
Yeah. I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
난 본 조비가 아니죠
당신이 찾는 매력남도
아니구요
Or someone you find attractive.
그저... 당신의 감정이
달라지기만 바랍니다
I just think, you know...
...that you might end up
feeling differently.
오해 말고 들으세요
I don't want this
to come out wrong...
...but you're awfully confident for a
guy I said I wasn't attracted to.
자신을 안 좋아한단 말을 들은
남자치곤 당당하시네요
멍청하기 그지없죠?
Stupidly charming, isn't it?
뭐 먹으러 갈래요?
너무 갑갑하네요
You wanna get something to eat?
This place is kind of depressing.
이 모든 걸 가능케 해주신
피트 베커 씨를 소개합니다
Now the man who made all of this
possible, Mr. Peter Becker.
One second.
잠깐만요
우리가 공생하기엔
이 도시가 너무 좁다
I don't think this town is big enough
for the both of us to relax in.
Draw!
뽑아라!
아무 짓도 안 했어
I wasn't doing anything.
또 그 여자가 긁냐?
What did she do now?
Just because she went to Yale, she
thinks she's the greatest actress...
예일 연극학교 출신이라고
대단한 여배우인 양 맨날...
...since sliced bread.
맥주병 얘기만 해
Ah, Sliced Bread.
A wonderful Lady Macbeth.
맥주병...
대단한 맥베스지
정말 싫어 죽겠어
하는 짓도 미워
I hate her. I hate her
with her "Oh, I'm so talented"...
난 재능이 너무 많아
난 너무 예뻐
...and "Oh, I'm so pretty,"
and "Oh, I smell so good."
난 향기도 좋아
I think somebody has a crush
on somebody.
누군가 누군가한테
반한 거 같다
제발 내 문제에만
신경 써줄래?
Can we please try and stay focused
on my problem here?
I'm talking about you,
you big, big freak.
지금 네 얘기야
이 위선자야!
You're out of your mind!
정신나갔군!
지난 48시간 동안 내내
그 여자 얘기만 했잖아
You've done nothing but talk
about her for 48 hours.
If you were in school, you'd be pulling
her pigtails and pushing her down now.
네가 초등학생이었으면
그 여자 머리나 잡아당기고
발이나 걸었을 거다
그래?
Then how come I keep thinking
about her...
근데 그 여자 생각만 하면
야한 것만 떠오르냐?
...in all these sexual scenarios
and stuff?
Happy? Is that what I'm
supposed to be, Vic? Happy?
행복?
이걸 행복이라고 해?
그럼 당신이 원하는
행복을 말해봐
Why don't you tell me what
you're supposed to be, huh?
Because I sure as hell can't
figure it out.
난 죽어도 모르겠으니까!
그건 아무 것도 아냐!
I talk to you, and it's nothing.
You look at me, and nothing.
날 봐, 아무 것도 아냐
아무 것도!
Nothing.
하늘을 나는 기분이오
You guys make me fly!
높이!
High!
내일 다시 해봅시다
Okay, we're gonna pick it up
here, tomorrow.
그럼 오늘은...
-Well, that was....
-Better?
- 나아졌죠?
- 네, 아주 많이요
Yeah, it was definitely...
좋아요... 잘 가요
...an improvement.
-Good night.
-Kate.
- 케이트?
- 네?
신발 저기 있어요
You forgot your shoes.
I'm probably gonna need those, huh?
맨발로 나갈 뻔 했네요
있잖아요...
Hey, listen...
커피 한 잔 할래요?
...you feel like getting
a cup of coffee?
Kate...
- 케이트
- 네?
...you ready to go?
- 준비됐어요?
- 네
좋아요, 아주 좋아요
Very nice. Very nice.
그럼...
- 내일 봐요
- 네, 그러죠
-See you tomorrow?
-Yeah. Sure.
- 잘 가요
-Right.
-Good night.
얘!
왜 스파이더맨이니?
Why isn't it "Spiderman"?
Like Goldman, Silverman?
골드맨, 실버맨도 있는데
그건 성이 아냐
Because it's not his last name.
- 아니야?
- 아니지
It isn't?
It's not, like...
필 스파이더맨 같은
이름은 없잖아
... Phil Spiderman.
그건 스파이더...
거미란 뜻이야
He's a Spider-...
... man.
골드맨은 성이니까
골드, 금이 아니지
You know, like, Goldman
is a last name.
But there's no Gold Man.
골드맨 영화도 재밌겠다
There should be a Gold Man!
- 나 왔어
- 안녕!
-How was work?
-Oh, great.
- 오늘 하루 어땠어?
- 좋았어
바닥에 주저앉은 것만 빼고
Although I did sit down
where there wasn't a chair.
By the way, Ross dropped by
a box of your stuff.
오빠가 네 물건이라고
상자를 놓고 갔어
그럴 줄 알았어
Oh. Well, I guess I had
that one coming.
다 버릴 거야
샴푸 같은 거나...
I'm just gonna throw it out.
It's probably just shampoo and
Something wrong?
왜 그래?
별거 아냐
No. Nothing.
골드맨은 어떤 힘이 있어?
So what kind of powers
would "Gold Man" have?
만지기만 하면 다 금이 돼
Okay. Well, he would turn things
to gold.
-And things that are already gold?
-His work is done.
어떤 게 금이 됐는데?
퇴근해서 몰라
Let's play my game.
- 이번엔 내 걸로 하자
- 좋아
All right, you yellow-bellied,
lily-livered
겁 많은 병아리,
소심한 병아리...
Draw!
뽑아라!
이것도 재밌다!
Yeah, it's fun.